Guide to the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives Vertical Files: Individuals ALBA.VF.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: ALBA Individual Files, 1
  - Hughes, Langston, 1902-1967 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hughes, William J., "Salud: Spain and the Return of the Inter...des, November 1996" (Typescript) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Huhle, Teresa: Spanish Civil War Monuments and the Politics o...see library for printed version) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hunter, John Porter (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Hunter, Oscar (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hurucz, John (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Hutchins, Evelyn, 1910-1982 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Hutner, Daniel (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Hynes, Harry (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Ibarruri, Dolores, 1895-1989 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Ibarruri, Dolores, 1895-1989: Writings and Speeches (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Iceland, Benjamin (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Indra, Jerome (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Ingalls, Robert Zane (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Inget, John (also Ingbert and Ingert) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Jackson, Burt Edward (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Jackson, Gabriel (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Jacobou, Andrew (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Jacobs, Deyo (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Jankovic, Matylda (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Jardass, Edo (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Jenkins, John Hollis (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Jensky, Toby, 1911-1995 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Jiminez, Mike (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Johanssen, Gustaf Ivar (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Johnson, Aaron Bernard (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Johnson, Allan (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Johnson, Ashley (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Johnson, Edward (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Johnson, Lloyd Edward (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Johnson, Richard (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Johnston, Ambrose (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Johnston, Charles Hitchcock (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Joliet-Curie, June (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Jones, David (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Jones, James M. (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Jones, Sheldon (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Jordan, Dennis (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Jordan, Frank (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Jorgensen, Hans Peder (Pete) (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Joynson, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Judt, Tony (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Junas, Stanley (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Kachadorian, David (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Kailin, Clarence S. (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Kambites, John (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Kapelner, Nathan (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Kaplan, Sam (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Kaplowitz, Kappy (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Kaplowitz, Morris (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Kartz, Max (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Kashtan, William (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Kasinap, Ben (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Katz, Hyman Jacob (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Katz, Isaac (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Katz, Max (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Katz, Sam (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Kaufman, Alfred Leo (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Kaufman, Rubin (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Kaufman, Sid (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Kaye, Conrad M. (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Kaye, George (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Kee, Salaria Lillie (a.k.a. Salaria Kea, later O'Reilly) (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Keeler, Addison (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Keen, Harry (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Keenan, Thomas, 1959- (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Keir, Duncan Jr. (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Keith, Charles Lawrence (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Keith, Irving (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Keller, Fred Paul (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Kelly, David Gillis (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Kelly, Thomas Joseph (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Kendall, Wilmoore, 1909-1967 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Kenner, Valentin (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Kenny, Dick (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1882-1971 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Kerhlicker, Anthony Peter (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Kerin, Armand (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Kilpatrick, Admiral (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Kipnis, Bertha (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Kish, Leslie, 1910-2000 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Kleber, General Emilio (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Kleidman, Larry (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Klein, Dr. Jack (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Klein, Herman "Gabby," see Rosenstein (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Klein, Seymour (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Kleinbordt, Paul (aka Steve "Pablo" Davis) (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Kleinman, Harry (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Kleinman, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Kline, Herbert (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Klonsky, Robert (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Knox, Bernard (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Kolarov, Peter (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Koll, Dr. Edwin (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Koltsov, Mikhail, 1898-1942 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Koneski, Sam (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Korb, Max (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Kormes, Karl (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Kornblat, Sam (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Kornblum, Morris (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Kornblutt, Joel (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Koslow, Alan (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Kotler, Ben (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kozar, John, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Kozlowski, Ernest (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Krafsur, Samuel (Bill) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Kramer, Jacob A., 1892-1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Krangel, Murray (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Krassavin, Michael (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Krauss, Martin (Mac) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kruth, Helen Leiviska (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kuchinskas, Frank (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kunslich, Alexander (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kurtz, Sidney (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kusman, Felix, 1919-1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - La Vine, Bob (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Labanyi, Jo: Paper on ALBA Archives, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Lamb, Leonard (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Land, Sanford Carl (Sandy) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Landis, Arthur H., 1917-1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Langdon-Davies, John (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Lardner, James Phillips, 1914-1938 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Lardner, Ring, 1915-2000 I (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Lardner, Ring, 1915-2000 II (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Largo Caballero, Francisco, 1869-1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Laveck, Lew (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Law, Norman Emmet (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Law, Oliver (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Law, Oliver: T. Greiner Files (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Lawrence, Wiliam (Oversize) (Oversize Shared ALBA VF OS, Folder 22)
  - Leap, George (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Lecoeur, Auguste (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Lee, Gypsy Rose, 1914-1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Lee, Laurie (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Lefkowitz, Louis (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Lehane, Michael (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Leider, Ben, 1901-1937 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Leight, Clara (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Leiserowitz, Sol (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Leiviska, George (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Lemke, Otto Ernest (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Lending, Edward Isaac, 1912-2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Lenthier, John (Arthur) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Leon, Francisco Trejo (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lerner, Isaiah (Sol) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Lerner, James (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Levenson, Leonard (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Levenson, Leonard, "US Communists in Spain" (Political Affairs, 1986) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Levi, Lieto Madjez (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Levick, Lionel (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Levine, Harry (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Levine, Louis S. (Steve) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Levine, Maurice, 1907- (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Levine, Philip: Lecture on SCW Poetry (NYU) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Levine, Robert (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Levinger, Samuel Harold (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Levitas, Maurice (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Levy, Bert, b. 1897 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Lewis, Abraham (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Lewis, Charles Howard (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Lichter, Harry E. (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Lidz, Harry (Arthur) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Linn, Sidney (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Lipton, David R., 1947- (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Lisberg, Norman (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - List, Paul (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Lister, Enrique (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Lloyd-George, David, "Spain and Britain" (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Lloyd, Tom (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Llubere, Rafael Angel (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Loesch, Michael Victor (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Logan, John (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Longo, Luigi, 1900- (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Lopez, Jules Herman (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Lopez, Raphael (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Lopoff, Aaron (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Lord, Frederick (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Lossowski, Vincent, 1914-1984 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Love, Vaughn (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Love, Vaughn: Autobiography (typescript) (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Low, Mary (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Lucid, John M. (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Ludwick, Percy (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Luftig, Joe (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Lustgarten, Larry (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Lustiger, Arno (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Lutga, Paul (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Lyons, Edwin (Lebovitz) (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Maceachron, Paul Norton (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Mack, Henry (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - MacKay, Anthony (aka Anthony Michaels) (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Macleod, Donald (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Madigan, Frank (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Magrini, Peter M. (aka Guido Brogelli; Guillermo Masana) (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Mail, Jack (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Maki, Martin (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Malbin, Dorothy Fontaine (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Malbin, Virginia (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Male, Douglas Wayne (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Mallem, Lloyd Mallan (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Malofsky, Harold (Meloff) (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Malraux, Andre, 1901-1976 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Mandel, Emanuel (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Mani, Freeman (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Mannert, Robert: "Letter to Spain" (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Manuel, Frank Edward.: "What Is Happening In Spain?" (Harvard...School Broadcast, July 29, 1939) (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Margolis, Irving (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Margrave, Dr. Rodger J. (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Marion, George, 1905- (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Markert, Clement Lawrence, 1917- (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Markovich, Mirko, 1907- (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Markovich, Mirko: Book in Serbian (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Marlow, Inver (aka John Scott) (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Marti-Ibanez, Felix, 1915-1972 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Martin, Fredericka I. (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Martinez, John (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Marty, Andr, b.1886 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Marzani, Carl (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Mates, David (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Matthews, Herbert Lionel, 1900- (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mattson, Matti (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mazzetti, Frank (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - McCarthy, Bill (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - McCasland, Virgil Ivan (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - McCuistion, William C. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - McDaniels, Eulard Luchell (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - McLaughlin, Paddy (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - McNeil, Allan (aka Johnson, Allan) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - McStravick, James T. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Medina Sidonia, 1936-, Duchess of (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Megquier, Henry Benn (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Melkisitian, Andrew (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Mendelson, Wilfred, 1915-1938 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mensh, Harry (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Merims, Sonia (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Merino, Pedro Mateo (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Merriman, Robert Hale (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Michalis, M. (photographer) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Mickenberg, Morris (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Mihajlovic (Mihailovic) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Miller, Alex (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Miller, Arthur, 1915-2005 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Miller, David M. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Miller, Fred Ralph (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Miller, Henry, 1891-1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Miller, William Colfax (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Miller, William Newton (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Millstone, George (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Miltenberger, John A. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Miltiades, Andres (Miltiadou, Andrew Jacobu) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Milton, Harry (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Milward Barnett, Monica: Diary (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Minor, Robert, 1884-1952 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Mitchell, Andrew (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Monks, Joe (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Mooney, Andrew (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Moran, Marden (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Morell, Bill (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Morgan, Crawford (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Moro, Sofia: Photo Collection (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Morris, Virgil (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Moskowitz, Ignatz (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Mougiannis, Christos (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Mouton, Roy (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Muller, Gerritt (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Murra, John V. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Muscala, Edward (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1912-1997 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Navarro, Vincente: "The Lincoln Brigade: Some Comments on U.S. History" (Monthly Review, 1986) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Neafus, Ralph Lawrence (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Negrin, Juan (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Neipold, Paul (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Nelson, Cary (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Nelson, Steve, 1903- (I) (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Nelson, Steve, 1903- (II) (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Nelson, Steve, 1903- (Oversized) (Oversize Shared ALBA VF OS, Folder 23)
  - Neugass, James, 1905-1949 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Newman, Sol (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Newton, Saul (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Niebuhr, Hans (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Nitzberg, Leo (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Noachowitz, Irving (aka Norman, Irving) (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Nobel, Harry (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Noble, Harry (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Noble, Marion (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Nomad, Max Collection (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Norman, Irving, 1906-1989, See Noachowitz, Irving (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - North, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Nusser, Charles (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Oak, Liston M. (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - O'Brien, Mary Wallner (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Obriot, Tersil (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - O'Casey, Sean, 1880-1964 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Oderaka, William (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Oehler, Hugo (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - O'Flaherty Brothers (Charles, Frank and Edward), See Flaherty Brothers (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - O'Flaherty, Tom (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - O'Hara, James B. (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Ojst, Emil (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Olson, Leonard (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - O'Malley, Thomas W. (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Opara, Rudolph (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1904-1967 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Oram, Harold L. (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - O'Riordan, Michael (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Ornitz, Lou (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Orr, Charles and Lois (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Orwell, George, 1903-1950 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Osheroff, Abe (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Osipenko, Alexander S. (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Ost, Milt (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - O'Toole, Lawrence (Larry) (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Pacey, Donald W.R. (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Page, Tom (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Palmer, Margaret, "Letters from Spain, 1936-1939 (Archives of American Art, 1986) (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Panaszewic, John (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Pappas, Nick (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Parker, Charles Augustus (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Parker, DeWitt Webster, 1910-1938 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Parker, Dorothy, 1893-1967 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Parker, Max and Mary (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Parks, John William (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Paselli, Luigi (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Pasht, William (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Pasternack, Alvin (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Pasternack, David (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Pasternak, Hersh (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Patai, Frances (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1901-1994: VALB Tribute to (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Payne, Stephan M.: "American Action and Reaction to the Spani...vil War" (typescript; photocopy) (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Peck, James L. H. (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Pena, Leoncio (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Penrod, John Arthur (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Perrone, John (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Persoff, James (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Peters, Frederick Anderson (a.k.a. Palmer Stanley Lucas) (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Peters, George (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Peters, Robert, 1924- (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Petrella, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Pflaum, Irving B., 1907- (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Phetteplace, Manch O. (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Pidolin, Si (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Piekarski, John (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Pike, William (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Pike, William: "Dr. Pike's Spanish War," by Paul Margolis (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Pirie, Frank B. (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Pitt, James Albert (a.k.a. James Edward) (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Pitzer, John Charles (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Plotnick, Henry (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Polansky, Samuel (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Poling, Eugene Debs (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pollitt, Harry (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Polo, Higins (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Polon, Marjorie, 1924-1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Popovic, Koca (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Portnow, Irving (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Posner, Dr. John Jacob (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Postek, Stanley, 1912-1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Prager, Ted (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Prago, Albert (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Prago, Albert: Spanish Civil War Curriculum (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Preston, Paul (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Prince, Clarence I. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Pringle, Claude (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Prowell, Alpheus (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Pujol, Antonio (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Quiggle, Harlan (Gerry) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Quintanilla, Lous (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Raacke, Peter Ferdinand Edward (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Rabinowitz, Louis (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Radacoy, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Radosh, Ronald (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Ragner, Albin (Ragawskas; Ragowsky) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Ramer, Aaron (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Randall, Harry W., 1915- (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Ransom, Marcus (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Rappaport, Israel (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Rappoport, Irving (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Rauert, Henry George (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Rauschwald, Mark (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Raven, Robert J. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Ray, Thomas J. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Read, Patrick (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Reed, Peter Leroy (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Reed, Robert, 1914- (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Reeves, Otto Coleman (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Reid, Arnold (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Rein, David (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Renn, Ludwig, 1889- (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Rhetta, Virgil (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Richards, Frank (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Richardson, R, 1931-: Articles on the International Brigades and Militias (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Richman, Benjamin (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Riffe, Carl Herman (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Rifkin, Irving (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Ripps, Alfred (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Rissane, Tom (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Roach, Douglas (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Robbins, Al (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Robbins, Jerome (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Roberson, James (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Roberts, Hilda Bell (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Robertson, Milton (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Robinson, Frenchy (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Robinson, John Quigley "Robbie" (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Robles, Jose Maria Gil, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Rochester, Sterling Taylor (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Rodriguez, Julius (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Rody, John (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Rody, John (Oversized) (Oversize Shared ALBA VF OS, Folder 24)
  - Rolfe, Edwin, 1909-1954 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Rolfe, Mary (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Rol-Tanguy, Henri, 1908- (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Romer, Sam (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Romero, Ernest and Lois (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Romerstein, Herbert (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Romerstein, Herbert (donor): Selected Files from the International Brigades Archive, Moscow (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Roosevelt, Pat (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Rosario, Conrado Figueros (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Rose, Oliver Charles (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Rosen, Alex (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Rosenberg, Leo (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Rosenblatt, Sidney (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Rosenstein, Herman, 1915- (also Gabby Klein) (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Rosenstein, Sidney (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Rosenstone, Robert (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Rosner, Hy (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Ross, Adolph (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Ross, Adolph: Biographical Dictionary Project (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Rossen, John (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Roth, Charles (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Rowlson, Lester L. (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Royce, Edward Andrew (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Rubin, Harry (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Rubin, Henry (Hank) (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Rucker, James Bernard, 1912-1992 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Rudner, Sid (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Rusciano, Richard (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Russell, Ross (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Ryan, Frank, 1902-1944 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Ryan, William G. (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Sacalauskas, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Sack, Ely Joseph, 1937-1992 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Saindon, Arthur (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Saks, Harry (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Sala Perez, Paulino (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Salvini, Fred (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Sanchez Amades, Vincente (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Saroff, Sophie, 1896- (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Sasnoff, Abe (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Sayles, John, 1950-: "But What about the Guys in the Lincoln Brigade?" (Monthly Review, 1980) (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Scanlon, Charles Anthony (Scarpello, Charles) (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Schechter, Rubin (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Schiff, Samuel (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Schindler, Harry (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Schmidt, (James) Norman (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Schneider, Eddie August (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Schoenberg, Harry (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Schofs, Fred (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Schrenzel, Isadore (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Schrieber, Paul (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Schuetrum, Walter (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Schulman Durem, Rebecca (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Schultz, Elias (Dutch) (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Schutt, Wilhelm (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Schwab, Irving (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Schwartz, Stephen: "Reading the Runes: New Perspectives on the SCW." (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Schwartz, Stephen: Review of Stanley Payne (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Schwartzberg, Max (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Schwarz, Abe (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Schwerner, Murray (Murf) (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Seborer, Max (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Secundy, Lewis (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Seeger, Pete (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Segal, Edith (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Selby, Vernon Romayne (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Seldes, George (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Selles, Chang (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Selligman, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Semons, Edwin (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Semprun, Jorge, 1923-2011 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Sender, Andrea (Sister Benedicta) (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Sennett, William, 1914- (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Serge, Victor, 1890-1947 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Service, Elman Rogers, 1915- (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Severdia, George Anthony (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Shafran, Jack (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Shaker, Kenneth R. (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Shapin, Danny (Shapiro, David Daniel) (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Sheean, Vincent, 1899-1975: on Dr. Barsky (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Sheehan, Roy (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Sherman, Alfred (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Sherman, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Shields, Art, 1888- (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Shipman, Evan (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Shirai, Jack (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Shirer, William Lawrence, 1904-1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Shosteck, Sidney (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Shufer, Max (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Shulman, Jack (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Siegel, Joseph Isaac (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sills, Ben (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sills, Samuel (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Silverstein, Esther (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Simon, John L. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Simon, Mildred Rackley, 1906-2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1878-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Skolnik, Abraham (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Slater, Carl (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Slotin, Louis S. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Small, Charles (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Smith, David (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Smith, Harold, 1912-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Owen Jefferson (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Randall, 1917-1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Smorodin, Abe (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Solodkin, Leo (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Soriano Villa, Manuel (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sorkin, Rose (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sossenko, George (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Southworth, Herbert Rutledge (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Spiller, Sam (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Sramek, Martin (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Staats, Frank (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Stadt, Zachary M. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Stamm, Morris (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Stanley, Al (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Stanley, Fred (Box 8, Folder 32)